[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which part of the body is decomposed last, but before the bones?", "correct_answer": "Hair", "incorrect_answers": ["Cartilages", "Nails", "Gall Bladder"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The Peshtigo Fire (in Wisconsin and Michigan) occurred on the same day as the Great Chicago Fire.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "It has been calculated that human beings can distinguish this many different colors.", "correct_answer": "10 millions", "incorrect_answers": ["10 000", "256", "260 000"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The Cross Channel Euroregion includes France, the UK and what other country?", "correct_answer": "Belgium", "incorrect_answers": ["Ireland", "Spain", "Netherlands"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Pre-eclampsia, thought to be caused by inflammatory mediators, is a medical condition associated with which of these?", "correct_answer": "Pregnancy", "incorrect_answers": ["Eye infections", "Brain tumor", "Bronchitis"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What word means fear of animals?", "correct_answer": "Zoophobia", "incorrect_answers": ["Pyrophobia", "Xenophobia", "Tachophobia"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In The Crow movie, what song is playing in the scenes where Eric is leaping from rooftop to rooftop?", "correct_answer": "Dead Souls - Nine Inch Nails", "incorrect_answers": ["Burn - The Cure", "COlor me once - Violent Femmes", "Big Empty - Stone Temple Pilots"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Talia Shire is probably best known for playing Adrian Pennino in the awesome Rocky movies. What was her characters name in the Godfather movies?", "correct_answer": "Connie Corleone", "incorrect_answers": ["Theresa Hagen", "Mrs. Marcia Roth", "Kay Corleone"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What type of character is Anna Sage, played by actress Branka Katic in the Public Enemies movie from 2009?", "correct_answer": "Prostitute", "incorrect_answers": ["FBI agent", "John Dillingers mother", "Murderer"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "\u201cThe art of protecting flat surfaces from the weather and exposing them to the critic\u201d is satirist Ambrose Bierce\u2019s definition for which of these activities?", "correct_answer": "Painting", "incorrect_answers": ["Sculpturing", "Repairing", "Safeguarding"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who do Benjamins children go to stay with in the movie The Patriot?", "correct_answer": "Aunt Charlotte", "incorrect_answers": ["The Howard family", "The Smith family", "Uncle Sam"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What was Escobars last line of dialogue in the movie Chinatown?", "correct_answer": "Just get him the hell out of here", "incorrect_answers": ["Forget it Jake, its Chinatown", "I dont care", "Halt!!"]}]